Guide to the Miscellaneous human sexuality periodicals,circa 1950-2003
Miscellaneous human sexuality periodicals,circa 1950-2003
- Network News (National Network) (Box 6)
  Publisher: National Network
- Network News (The Newsletter of UCLA's LGBT Faculty/Staff Network) (Box 6)
  Subject: College/University, Education, Occupation Based Organizations, Lesbian, Bisexual, Gay, Transgender, 1990s
  Publisher: UCLA LGBT Faculty/Staff Network
- Networker, The (A publication of the Rural AIDS Network) (Box 6)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, Medicine, Health, Politics, Legal
  Publisher: Rural AIDS Network
- New Boston Review (Box 6)
  Subject: Literary, Entertainment, 1970s, Race
  Publisher: Boston Critic, Inc.
  Publication City: Somerville, MA
- New England Gay, Lesbian & Bisexual Veterans, Inc. Newletter (NEGLBV) (Box 6)
  Subject: Veterans, Military, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Politics, Occupation Based Organizations, 1990s
  Publisher: New England Gay, Lesbian & Bisexual Veterans, Inc. (NEGLBV)
  Publication City: Dorchester, MA
- New Hampshire Pride Reporter (Box 6)
  Subject: Politics, Pride Parade and Events, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, News, Community
  Publisher: New Hampshire Pride
  Publication City: Danville, NH
- New Horizon (Box 6)
  Subject: Lesbian seperatists, Gay liberation movement, Gay, Lesbian, Men, Women, Feminist, 1970s, News, Pride Parade and Events
  Publisher: Parlee Entertainment, Inc.
  Publication City: Willston Part, NY
- New Voice: Gay News for Texas and Louisiana, The (Box 6)
- New York Citizens' AIDS Lobby Alert (Box 6)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, Politics, Legal, 1990s, News
  Publisher: New York Citizens' AIDS Lobby
- New York City AIDS Lobby Alert (Box 6)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, Politics
- New York City Volunteer Update (Box 6)
  Subject: Community service, 1980s, Gay, Lesbian, Community
  Publisher: New York City Volunteer Update
- New York Insider, The (Box 6)
  Subject: Entertainment, Cruising, Gay, Lesbian, Drag, Transgender, Bisexual, 1980s
  Publisher: Insider Marketing
- New York State Coalition of Gay Organizations (NYSCGO) (Box 6)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Community, Occupation Based Organizations, Politics, Legal, Gay liberation movement, 1970s,
  Publisher: New York State Coalition of Gay Organizations (NYSCGO)
- New York State Lesbian & Gay Lobby Newsletter (Box 6)
- News & Views (Parents and Friends of Lesbians and Gays of Denver [PFLAG]) (Box 6)
  Subject: Parenting, Families, Gay, Lesbian, 1990s
  Publisher: Parents and Friends of Lesbians and Gays of Denver (PFLAG)
- News from ICAAC '90 (Box 6)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, Medicine, News, Health, 1990s
  Publisher: ICAAC
- News From Lambda Legal Defense & Education Fund, Inc. (Box 6)
  Subject: Legal, Politics, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, 1980s
  Publisher: Lambda Legal Defense & Education Fund, Inc.
- News from Rutgers GALA (Rutgers University Gay and Lesbian Alumni/ae) (Box 6)
  Subject: Education, College/University, Gay, Lesbian, 1990s, History
  Publisher: Rutgers University Gay and Lesbian Alumni/ae
  Publication City: New Brunswick, NJ
- News from the Fund For Reunion/ Princeton GALA (Box 6)
  Subject: College/University, Education, Community, Princeton University, 1980s
  Publisher: The Fund For Reunion/Princeton GALA
  Publication City: Princeton, NJ
- News Jersey: New Jersey Gay Coalition newsletter (Box 6)
  Publication City: (New Brunswick, NJ)
- News Link (Project of Community Link) (Box 6)
  Subject: News, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Transgender, Community, 1990s, Pride Parade and Events
  Publisher: Community Link, Inc.
  Publication City: Fresno, CA
- News of Lesbian and Gay Teachers (Box 6)
  Subject: Gay, Education, Schools, Occupation Based Organizations, Lesbian, 1990s, Youth, Safer sex, Contraception
  Publisher: AFT National Gay and Lesbian Caucus
- News, The (A Publication of The Atlanta Gay Center) (Box 6)
  Subject: Community, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, 1980s, News
  Publisher: The Atlanta Gay Center, Inc.
- Newsday (Box 6)
  Subject: News, 1980s, Gay, Lesbian
- Newsletter (Houston Gay & Lesbian Political Caucus [GLPC]) (Box 6)
  Subject: Politics, Gay, Lesbian, Legal, Gay liberation movement, 1980s
  Publisher: Houston Gay & Lesbian Political Caucus (GLPC)
- Newsletter (International Gay Rights Congress) (Box 6)
  Subject: Politics, Legal, 1970s, Gay, Lesbian
  Publisher: International Gay Rights Congress
  Publication Country: Scotland
  Publication City: Edinburgh
- Newsletter (Pennsylvania Lesbian/Gay Support Network) (Box 6)
  Subject: Lesbian, Gay, 1980s, Community, Pride Parade and Events
  Publisher: Pennsylvania Lesbian/Gay Support Network
- Newsletter (Right to Privacy Political Action Committee) (Box 6)
  Subject: Politics, Legal, Gay liberation movement, Lesbian, Gay, 1980s
  Publisher: Right to Privacy Political Actions Committee
- Newsletter (Tompkins County Task Force for Battered Women) (Box 6)
  Subject: Women and violent crimes, Women, Cornell University, HIV/AIDS, 1990s
  Publisher: Tompkins County Task Force for Battered Women/ Child Sexual Abuse Project (TCTFBW/CSAP)
- Newsletter of the ACLU Gay Rights Chapter, The (Box 6)
  Subject: Legal, Gay, Lesbian, Politics, Gay liberation movement, 1970s
  Publisher: American Civil Liberties Union, Gay Rights Chapter (ACLU)
- Newsletter of the Lavender Left (Box 6)
  Subject: Politics, Gay, Lesbian, Cruising, Legal
  Publisher: Lavender Left
- Newsletter, The (Cream City Business Association) (Box 6)
  Subject: Occupation Based Organizations, Politics, Legal, 1980s, Gay, Lesbian, Gay liberation movement, HIV/AIDS
  Publisher: Cream City Business Association (CCBA)
- Newsnotes (The Feminist Press) (Box 6)
  Subject: Feminist, Books, Book reviews, Schools, Youth, Gender issues, Women
  Publisher: The Feminist Press
  Publication City: Old Westbury, NY
- Night Life (Blueboy Presents) (Box 6)
  Subject: Cruising, Gay, Legal, Lesbian, Politics, News, 1970s, Gay liberation movement
  Publisher: California Nightlife, Inc.
- Nightlife (Box 6)
  Publisher: (Blueboy)
- Niteline (Box 6)
  Subject: Pride Parade and Events, Gay, Lesbian, Political, Legal, 1980s, Community, News
  Publisher: River Entertaining Inc.
- NJ Act Up (Box 6)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, Gay, Lesbian, Community, Health, Politics, Legal, 1980s
  Publisher: NJ Act Up (NJ AIDS Coalition to Unleash Power)
  Publication City: Teaneck, NJ
- NJWAN News (New Jersey Women and AIDS Network) (Box 6)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, Women, 1990s, Health, Medicine
  Publisher: New Jersey Women and AIDS Network (NJWAN)
- NMAC Healer (National Minority AIDS Council) (Box 6)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, People of Color, 1990s, Health, Occupation Based Organizations
  Publisher: NMAC (National Minority Aids Council)
- NMAC Update (National Minority AIDS Council) (Box 6)
  Publisher: NMAC (National Minority AIDS Council)
- NMAS (New Mexico AIDS Services) (Box 6)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, 1990s, Communit service, Psychology, Therapy
  Publisher: New Mexico AIDS Services, Inc.
- NOGLS Newsline (National Organization of Gay and Lesbian Scientists) (Box 6)
  Subject: Occupation Based Organizations, Gay, Lesbian, Community, 1980s, College/University, Education
  Publisher: National Organization of Gay and Lesbian Scientists (NOGLS)
- North Eastern Pennsylvania Gay Alliance (NEPGA) (Box 6)
  Subject: 1980s, Gay, Mass Media, Lesbian
  Publisher: North Eastern Pennsylvania Gay Alliance
  Publication City: Shavertown, PA
- Northern Lambda Nord (English and French language) (Box 6)
  Subject: Community, News, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Legal, Politics, Travel, Gay liberation movement
  Publisher: Northern Lambda Nord (NLN)
- Northwest Journal, The (Box 6)
  Subject: 1980s, Gay, Lesbian, Community, News, Alternative local newspaper, Families, Politics, Legal
  Publisher: J.T.&A., Inc.
- NOVA Law Review (and Los Angeles Times insert on HIV/AIDS and the law) (Box 6)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, Legal, Politics, Medicine, Health, Gay, Lesbian, 1980s, Race, Education, Schools, College/University,
  Publisher: NOVA Southeastern University
  Publication City: Fort Lauderdale, FL
- NOW York Woman, The (Box 6)
  Subject: Feminist, Women, Alternative local newspaper, Politics, Legal, Gender issues, 1980s
  Publisher: National Organization for Women (NOW), New York Chapter, Inc.
- Now, Voyagers! (The Newsletter for Gay Travelers) (Box 6)
  Publisher: NOW, VOYAGERS!
- Nurturing News (a quaterly forum for nuturing men...) (Box 6)
  Subject: Men, Gay, Families, Parenting, Education, Youth, 1980s
  Publisher: Nurturing News
- NYSCGO Political Newsletter (New York State Coalition of Gay Organizations) (Box 6)
- NYPAC: New York Political Action Council (Box 6)
  Subject: Politics, Legal, Gay liberation movement, Gay, Lesbian, 1970s, 1980s
  Publisher: New York Political Action Council (NYPAC)
- Off Center (a publication of the Center for LGBT Life, Duke University) (Box 6)
  Subject: LGBT, Duke University, Youth, College/University, Education, Youth
  Publisher: Center for LGBT Life, Duke University
  Publication City: Durham, NC
- Office Workers News (OWN) (Box 6)
  Subject: Occupation Based Organizations, Labor, 1970s, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual
  Publisher: Office Workers Network
- OGRC (Ohio Gay Rights Coalition) Newsletter (Box 6)
  Subject: Gay, Gay liberation movement, 1970s, Lesbian, Politics, Legal, Community
  Publisher: Ohio Gay Rights Coalition
  Publication City: Columbus, OH
- OIM Newsletter (Out In Montana) (Box 6)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Medicine, Health, Gay liberation movement, Politics, Legal, Prisoners, Gay prisoners
  Publisher: Out in Montana, Inc.
  Publication City: Missoula, MT
- On a Positive Note (The Newsletter of AIDS Service Organizations of Palm Beach County) (Box 6)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, Occupation Based Organizations, Medicine, Health, 1990s
  Publisher: People With AIDS Coalition of Palm Beach County (PWAC)
  Publication City: West Palm Beach, FL
- On Our Way (Lesbian Issue) (An Edmonton Women's Newspaper) (First Lesbian Newspaper in Canada) (Box 6)
  Subject: Lesbian, Women, Feminist, News, Alternative local newspaper, 1970s
  Publisher: Edmonton Women's Centre
  Publication City: Edmonton, AB
- On Parade (...On Parade!) (Box 6)
  Subject: Pride Parade and Events, 1980s, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Community, History
  Publisher: Lesbian/Gay Freedom Day Media Committee
- On Parade (Chicago's Gay & Lesbian Pride Week Newspaper) (Box 6)
  Subject: Pride Parade and Events, Gay, Lesbian, Community, 1980s, 1970s, History
  Publisher: The Gay & Lesbian Pride Week Planning Committee (Gay Pride Week Planning Committee, Inc.)
- On-Q Bay Area Magazine (Box 6)
  Subject: Queer, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Drag, Alternative local newspaper, News, Community, 1990s
  Publisher: On-Q Partners
- Open Closet, The (Southern Vermont Lesbians/Gay Men's Coalition) (Box 6)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Community, 1980s, Gay liberation movement, Legal, Politics
  Publisher: Southern Vermont Lesbians/Gay Men's Coalition
  Publication City: Brattleboro, VT
- Opening, The (Box 6)
  Subject: Literary, Women, 1970s, Lesbian, Transgender, Transexual, Feminist
  Publisher: KNOW, Inc.
  Publication City: Pittsburgh, PA
- Organizacion Nacional de La Salud de La Mujer Latina (National Latina Health Organization) (Spanish and English language) (Box 6)
  Subject: Health, Latina, Latino, Medicine, Safer sex, Contraception, HIV/AIDS, 1990s
  Publisher: Organizacion Nacional de La Salud de La Mujer (Latina/National Latina Health Organization)
- Organizing for Equality (Newsletter of the NGLTF Campus Project) (Box 6)
  Subject: NGLTF, Gay, Lesbian, Politics, Legal, Gay liberation movement, 1980s
- Oscar Wilde Memorial Bookshop Catalog (Box 6)
  Subject: Literary, Books, Book reviews, 1970s
  Publisher: Oscar Wilde Memorial Bookshop
- Ottawa Inside Out (Box 6)
  Subject: Politics, 1990s, Gay liberation movement, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Legal
  Publisher: Svend Robinson, MP (Ottawa Inside Out)
  Publication City: Ottawa, ON
- OU Update (Oklahoma University) (Box 6)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Education, Colllege/University, News
  Publisher: The University of Oklahoma Gay/Lesbian Alliance
  Publication City: Norman, OK
- Our Quarterly (Serving New Jersey's Gay, Lesbian and Bisexual Community) (Box 6)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, News, 1990s, 2000s, News, Alternative local newspaper, Community
  Publisher: It's Ours, Inc.
- Our Sorority (Mid-Atlantic Regional Journal of the Society for the Second Self and the Gateway Gender Alliance) (Box 6)
  Subject: Transgender, Transsexual, 1980s, Gender issues, Drag, Transvestite, Men, Women, Heterosexual
  Publisher: The Society for the Second Self and the Gateway Gender Alliance
  Publication City: Collingswood, NJ
- Our Times (Official Publication fo the Palmetto Gay/Lesbian Association) (Box 6)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, 1980s, Pride Parade and Events, Community
  Publisher: Palmetto Gay/Lesbian Association
  Publication City: Greenville, SC
- Our Toronto Weekly (Box 6)
  Subject: 1980s, Directory, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Pride Parade and Events, Entertainment
  Publisher: Gold-Bar Enterprises
- Out & Out Toronto (Box 6)
  Subject: Sports, Travel, Recreation, Gay, Lesbian, 1980s
  Publisher: Out & Out Toronto
- OUT (Newsletter of the Gay Student Union of the University of Delaware) (Box 6)
  Subject: College/University, Education, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, 1980s, Community
  Publisher: The University of Delaware Gay Student Union
  Publication City: Newark, DE
- Out and About (Rochester, NY) (Box 6)
  Subject: Gay, Sports
  Publication City: Rochester, NY
- Out Charlotte (A Cultural Festival Celebrating The Lesbian/Gay/Bisexual/Transgender Community) (Box 6)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Transgender, Pride Parade and Events, Queer, Community, Alternative local newspaper, 1990s
  Publisher: OutCharlotte, Inc.
- Out for Good Boston Pride 1987 (17 Years of Lesbian and Gay Pride in Boston) (Box 6)
  Subject: Pride Parade and Events, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, History, Community, 1980s
- Out In Florida (Box 6)
  Subject: Entertainment, Gay, 1980s, Men, Cruising, Directory, Classifieds
  Publisher: Chiswick Advertising, Inc.
- Out In NY '94 (Box 6)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Entertainment, 1990s, Pride Parade and Events, Sports, Recreation, Queer, Drag
  Publisher: Out IN NY '94
- Out in the Big Sky (Montana Lesbian Coalition) (Box 6)
  Subject: Lesbian, Legal, Politics, News, Women, Recreation
  Publisher: Montana Lesbian Coalition
  Publication City: Helena, MT
- Out Write (A Poetry Journal by Gay, Lesbian, and Bisexual Youth) (Box 6)
  Subject: Literary, Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, Youth, Queer, Safer sex
  Publisher: Lambda Community Center
- OUT East (Visitor's Directory & Map) (Box 6)
  Subject: Travel, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Directory, 2000s
  Publisher: Pride Guide Publishing
- OUTlines (Box 6)
  Subject: Entertainment, Gay, Lesbian, Directory, News, Community
  Publisher: AllSet Corporation
- Outlook (Box 6)
- Outlook (Columbus, Ohio) (Box 6)
  Subject: Alternative local newspaper, 1990s, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, News, Community, Politics, Legal
  Publisher: Outlook Publishing, Inc.
- Outpostings Community Center News (Serving the lesbian, gay, bisexual, and transgender communities of Champaign-Urbana and surrounding areas) (Box 6)
  Subject: Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, Transgender, Community, News, Community service, 1990s, Directory
  Publisher: OUTpost Community Center
  Publication City: Champaign, IL
- Outword! (Box 6)
  Subject: Entertainment, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, 1990s, Politics, News, Community, Health, Book reviews
  Publisher: Pride Publishing, Inc.
  Publication City: Calgary, AB
- Outwords (Buffalo's Queer Communitites' Newspaper) (Box 6)
  Subject: Safer sex, Contraception, Race, Queer, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Legal, News, Politics, HIV/AIDS, Military, 1990s
  Publisher: SKA Graphics, Ltd.
- Outwords (The Out For Equity Newsletter) (Box 6)
  Subject: Education, College/University, Schools, Families, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Community service, 1990s
  Publisher: Out for Equity
- P.O.L.: Proud. Out. Loud. (News from the New Mexico Lesbian & Gay Political Alliance) (Box 6)
  Subject: Politics, Legal, Gay, Lesbian, 1990s, Gay liberation movement
  Publisher: New Mexico Lesbian & Gay Political Alliance
  Publication City: Albuquerque, NM
- PAAC Notes (Newjournal of the Physicians Association for AIDS Care) (Box 6)
  Subject: Health, HIV/AIDS, Occupation Based Organizations, Medicine, 1990s
  Publisher: PAAC Publishing, Inc.
- Pace! (Box 6)
  Publication City: (Washington, DC)
- Pacific Passage (Box 6)
  Subject: 1980s, Alternative local newspaper, News, Calandar, Gay liberation movement, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Performing arts, Arts
  Publisher: Lambda Arts, Inc.
- Pages, The (A Comprehensive Directory of Hawaii's Gay-Supportive Businesses, Organizations, and Services) (Box 6)
  Subject: Directory, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Business, Community, 1990s
  Publisher: Lifestyle Publishing Co., Inc.
- Pallas Athena (The Network/Publication by & for Woman Veterans) (Box 6)
  Subject: Women, Veterans, Military, Lesbian, Heterosexual, 1990s
  Publisher: The Pallas Athena Network
  Publication City: New Market, VA
- Palouse Gay News (formerly "Update for Action") (Box 6)
  Subject: News, Alternative local newspaper, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, 1980s, College/University
  Publisher: North West Gay Peoples Alliance, Inc. / Gay People's Allance, Washington State University
  Publication City: Moscow, ID
- Parents & Friends of Gays ("National News") (now PFLAG) (Box 6)
  Subject: Families, Parenting, Gay, News, Lesbian, Community, 1970s, 1980s
  Publisher: NF/PFG, Inc.
- Parents and Friends of Gays of Phoenix (Box 6)
  Subject: Families, Parenting, Gays, Lesbians, 1980s, Community, Heterosexual
  Publisher: Parents and Friends of Gays of Phoenix
  Publication City: Phoenix, AZ
- Parents FLAG Atlanta (Parents, Families & Friends of Lesbians and Gays) (Box 6)
  Subject: Families, Gay, Lesbian, Heterosexual, Parenting, News
  Publisher: Parents, Families & Friends of Lesbians and Gays, Atlanta (PFLAG)
- Parkdale Gayzette, The (Box 6)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, 1990s, Bisexual, Pride Parade and Events
- Passion Brigade (Embracing The Lesbian And Gay Freedom Movement) (Box 6)
  Subject: Sexual liberation, Gay liberation movement, Gay, Lesbian, 1990s, Feminist, Anti-sexist men, Zine
  Publisher: Passion Brigade / LGFM (Lesbian and Gay Freedom Movement)
- Patchwork (California Association of Gay Student Organizations) (Box 6)
  Subject: 1970s, Gay, Lesbian, Politics, Legal, Education, Schools, College/University, Occupation Based Organizations
  Publisher: California Association of Gay Student Organizations
  Publication City: Venice, CA
- PDC Notes (Partisan Defense Committee) (Class-Struggle Defense Notes) (Box 6)
  Subject: 1980s, Politics, Legal, Prisoners, Labor, Sexual liberation, Books, Sexual liberation
  Publisher: PDC (Partisan Defense Committee)
- PDQ (Publication of Digital Queers) (Box 6)
  Subject: 1990s, Queer, Occupation Based Organizations, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual
  Publisher: Digital Queers
- Peace Letter (Washington Peace Center) (Box 6)
  Subject: Race, Schools, Education, College/University, Gender issues, History, Politics, Legal, 1980s
  Publisher: Washington Peace Center
- Pentecostal Coalition (Newsletter of the Pentecostal Coalition for Human Rights / "Supporting Black, Hispanic, Women's, and Gay Liberation") (Box 6)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Women, Feminist, Race, Hispanic, Latino, Latina, Gay liberation movement, Legal, Politics, News, Religious: Pentecostal, Religious: Christian, Religious, African-American
  Publisher: The Pentecostal Coalition for Human Rights
- Perspectives (A special publication of the Canadian AIDS Society) (French and English Language) (Box 6)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, Health, Health, Occupation Based Organizations, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Race, Women, Men, Gender issues, Community, Disability Issues, 1990s
  Publisher: Canadian AIDS Society
- Phi Pi Epsilon (A New International Sorority for Femmepersonators) (Box 6)
  Subject: Transgender, Transsexual, Transvestite, Drag, Gender issues, Heterosexual, Men, Women, 1960s
  Publisher: Phi Pi Epsilon
- Philadelphia Area Gaylaxians Newsletter (Box 6)
  Subject: Gay trekkies, Gay, Entertainment, Community, 1990s
  Publisher: Philadelphia Area Gaylaxians
- PHOTOS Catalog (Box 6)
  Subject: Physique, Catalog, Men in art, Arts, Men, 1990s
  Publisher: PHOTOS Catalog
  Publication City: Santa Clara, CA
- Pillar (Utah's True Alternative Newspaper for the Gay and Lesbian Community) (Box 6)
  Subject: Alternative local newspaper, News, Gay, Lesbian, 1990s, Health, Community, Travel, Business, Religious, Entertainment
  Publisher: Pillar Publishing
  Publication City: Salt Lake City, UT
- Pink Ink (Thailand's Gay & Lesbian Monthly) (Box 6)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, 1990s, Transsexual, Safer Sex, Community, Community service
  Publisher: Nick Wilde and Jennifer Bliss
  Publication Country: Thailand
  Publication City: Bangkok
- Pink Pathways (Southwestern Ontario's Community Connection) (Box 6)
  Subject: Directory, 1990s, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Queer, Community
  Publisher: Pink Pathways Publishing
  Publication City: London, ON
- Pink Thylacines (The Magazine of the Tas. Gay & Lesbian Rights Group) (Box 6)
  Subject: Lesbian, Gay, 1990s, Gay liberation movement, Community, News, Religious: Anglican
  Publisher: The Tasmania Gay & Lesbian Rights Group
  Publication City: Hobart, TAS
- Pink Triangle Report, The (The Newsletter of Kansas City's Gay and Lesbian Political Coalition) (Box 6)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Politics, Legal, HIV/AIDS, Anti-violence, Gay liberation movement
  Publisher: The Pink Triangle Political Coalition
- Piss and Vinegar (Box 6)
  Author: Michael Petrelis Subject: 1980s, HIV/AIDS, 1990s, Politics, Legal, Gay liberation movement, Gay, Lesbian
  Publisher: Michael Petrelis
- plain brown rapper (An Information Digest) (Box 6)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, Gay, Lesbian, Parenting, Families, Politics, Schools, Education, Youth, Health, Medicine, Politics, Legal, Book reviews, 1980s, Race, African-American
  Publisher: Omnium Gatherum, Inc.
- Plain Talk (Box 6)
  Subject: Families, Gay, Lesbian, Parenting, 1990s, Youth
  Publisher: We Are Family Foundation
  Publication City: Charleston, SC
- Planned Parenthood Public Affairs (PPPA) Weekly Newsletter (Box 6)
  Subject: Health, Medicine, Sexual liberation, Contraception, Safer sex, 1980s, Politics, Legal
  Publisher: Planned Parenthood
- Pop Shop (Keith Haring) (Box 6)
  Subject: Catalog, Arts, HIV/AIDS, 1990s
  Publisher: The Estate of Keith Haring
- Power Exchange, The (A Newsletter for Women on the Sexual Fringe) (Box 6)
  Author: Pat Califia
  Subject: s/m, Fetish, Lesbian, Women, Gender issues, Transgender, 1980s, HIV/AIDS
  Publisher: Editrix Pat Califia
- Prairie Woman (A Newsletter of Saskatoon Women's Liberation) (Box 6)
  Subject: Feminist, Lesbian, Lesbian separatists, Women, Gender issues, Labor, Politics, Legal, Gay, Gay liberation movement, 1970s, 1980s
  Publisher: Saskatoon Women's Liberation
  Publication City: Saskatoon, SK
- Premiere (Box 6)
  Subject: Erotica, Gay male
  Publication City: (Minneapolis, Minn.)
- Prepare (National IMPACT Education Fund) (Box 6)
  Subject: Gay liberation movement, Gay, Lesbian, Legal, Politics, 1980s
  Publisher: National IMPACT Education Fund
- Pride Guide (Queens' First Pride Celebration / June 6th, 1993) (Box 6)
  Subject: Pride Parade and Events, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Community, Queer, 1990s
  Publisher: The Queens Lesbian and Gay PRIDE (QLGPC) Committee
- Pride Guide (Toronto) (French and English language) (Box 6)
  Subject: Pride Parade and Events, 2000s, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Transgender
  Publisher: Pride Toronto
- Pride Guide 2005 (The LOFT [The Lesbian and Gay Community Services Center]) (Box 6)
  Subject: Pride Parade adn Events, Queer, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, 2000s